<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <!-- Room Names -->
  <roomname.deck>Deck</roomname.deck>
  
  <biomename.openskies>Open Skies</biomename.openskies>
  <Override>
  <biomename.thegreatsea>The Great Void</biomename.thegreatsea>
  </Override>

  <missiontype.FleetVsFleetCombat>Fleet vs. Fleet</missiontype.FleetVsFleetCombat>
  <missionname.fleetmission>Search and destroy</missionname.fleetmission>
  <missiondescriptionneutral.fleetmission>A Coalition fleet has been dispatched from [location1] to destroy a renegade flotilla at the outskirts of [location2].</missiondescriptionneutral.fleetmission>
  <missiondescription1.fleetmission>A renegade flotilla has been detected at the outskirts of [location2]. Treason against the Europa Coalition is punishable by death—eliminate the renegades by any means necessary.</missiondescription1.fleetmission>
  <missiondescription2.fleetmission>You're a member of the Jovian Separatists, a group opposing the Europa Coalition. According to your informants at [location1], a Coalition fleet has just been dispatched on a mission to take down your flotilla. Eliminate their ships by any means necessary.</missiondescription2.fleetmission>
  <missionteam1.fleetmission>Coalition</missionteam1.fleetmission>
  <missionteam2.fleetmission>Jovian Separatists</missionteam2.fleetmission>
  <missionsuccess.fleetmission>The [loser] fleet has been defeated by the [winner]!</missionsuccess.fleetmission>
  <missionfailure.fleetmission>Neither fleet managed to destroy the enemies.</missionfailure.fleetmission>

  <entityname.mortarshell>Mortar Railgun Shell</entityname.mortarshell>
  <entitydescription.mortarshell>Similar to be regular railgun shell, but has a more intense arc due to added weight. Can be loaded with additional explosives explosives that detonate upon impact.</entitydescription.mortarshell>

  <Override>
  <entityname.combatdivingsuit>Combat Suit</entityname.combatdivingsuit>
  <entitydescription.combatdivingsuit>An agile, lightweight suit designed for combat. Offers some protection against damage and withstands pressure up to a depth of 5,700 meters.</entitydescription.combatdivingsuit>
  <entityname.slipsuit>Jetsuit</entityname.slipsuit>
  <entitydescription.slipsuit>A modified Combat Suit fitted with a jetpack to allow for aerial movement. Sadly, it is too heavy to run with, but the propulsion system can alleviate that. Withstands pressure up to a depth of 5,700 meters.</entitydescription.slipsuit>
  <entityname.underwaterscooter>Air Scooter</entityname.underwaterscooter>
  <entitydescription.underwaterscooter>A battery-powered aerial propulsion device.</entitydescription.underwaterscooter>
  <entityname.cargoscooter>Cargo Scooter</entityname.cargoscooter>
  <entitydescription.cargoscooter>An aerial scooter special-made to transport material in the air. While the scooter is too large to be stored in one's inventory, its heft is justified by its powerful propeller.</entitydescription.cargoscooter>
  <entitydescription.extinguisher>A handheld carbon dioxide extinguisher. Crouch whilst using this or you'll fly away!</entitydescription.extinguisher>
  <entitydescription.harpoongun>Launches harpoons, explosive harpoons, and alien harpoons. Can be used as a grappling hook gun.</entitydescription.harpoongun>
  <entitydescription.harpooncoilrifle>An advanced harpoon gun, powered by an energy source to launch harpoons at high velocities. Can be used as a grappling hook gun.</entitydescription.harpooncoilrifle>
  <entitydescription.spear>A harpoon for the harpoon gun. Can be used as a grappling hook.</entitydescription.spear>
  <entitydescription.alienspear>A harpoon for the harpoon gun, made of alien material. Can be used as a grappling hook.</entitydescription.alienspear>
  <entitydescription.spearunique>An antique spear named after a legendary captain. Can be used as a grappling hook.</entitydescription.spearunique>
  <!--<entitydescription.replaceme></entitydescription.replaceme>-->
  </Override>
</infotexts>